<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<Project Name="articlesBase">
<Page_Content>
<ContentNode>
<Content Mapping="Description1">Even if they may make it appear easy on television, with the right training, learning how to make cake decorations like a pro is not as hard believe.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title1">Discover How to Make Cake Decorations Like a Professional!</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description2">... . Cake pops are a delight to eat because of the irresistible taste and charming appearance. Try making this recipe for yummy cake pop that you will find very easy to make.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title2">Delectable Recipe for Cake Pops</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description3">Cake Decorations – The qualitysprinkles company - supplier of cake decorations, Chocolate Nonpareils, chocolate vermicelli, chocolate sprinkles, decorating equipment, baking Ingredients and sugar craft products</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title3">Make all your sweets look attractive and mouthwatering with all kinds of sprinkles</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description4">This article discover four type of cool and interesting Wedding Cake decorations ideas</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title4">Four Wedding Cake Decorations Ideas</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description5">Wedding is one such occasion which brings together people who witness the precious moments of two souls getting united in the sacred ceremony.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title5">Funny Cake Toppers for some hilarious moments at the Wedding</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description6">...  table every evening. For a special occasion, online cakes home delivery service for spending priceless moments ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title6">Online Cakes Home Delivery for Priceless Moments</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description7">Wholesale cake boxes may be bought at quite cheap rates if you choose the right place. If you do not intend to spend a lot of money on cake boxes, it is advisable to make a survey of many shops at</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title7">Cake Boxes Wholesale Information</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description8">Choosing the cake for your wedding can be both fun  ...  bakers let you taste the variety of cakes and fillings they offer, while showing you pictures of the many decorative cakes they offer. Let them know the look ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title8">Learn How to Choose a Great Wedding Cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description9">Want to discover the secrets of cake baking and cake art but don't have time or access to classes? You're in luck! Cake baking classes online can be a handy and gratifying way to learn industry secrets from the comfort of your own kitchen.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title9">Cake Baking Classes Online, the Perfect Way to Learn</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description10">The cake culture has slowly taken over the entire world. Cakes are now being frequently sent on occasions such as birthdays, weddings, engagements and anniversaries; and also sent on Valentine's Day, Mother's Day and other happy events.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title10">Create Magic with Midnight Cake Delivery Service</Content>
</ContentNode>
<ContentNode>
<Content Mapping="Description1">Choosing the right kind of cake to bake for cake decorating. Also what pans to choose for what type of cake you plan on decorating.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title1">Learning How To Make Cakes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description2">...  task to get involved in. You need cake decorating equipment, all the ingredients and other decorative accessories to bake a yummy cake. Here are some essential cookie decorating supplies and cake decorating equipment that are a must-have in ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title2">Bake a Delicious Cake for Your Family with Cake Decorating Supplies</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description3">There are varieties of cocoa powder that can be used in making bakery products. Cacao Barry is world's largest producer in manufacturing cocoa powder. Use of cocoa powder in bakery products can give mouthwatering delicacies.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title3">Give your mouths a treat by some delicious pastries, cakes, and chocolates made with cocoa powder</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description4">Trends in wedding cakes, like all other wedding details, evolve with  ...  this list of top trends for wedding cakes.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title4">7 New Trends for Wedding Cakes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description5">...  think of dream wedding cakes, you most likely believe of tiered wedding cakes that you simply see everywhere in bakeries. These tiered cakes are existing at virtually all weddings, though ...  having a cupcake tree or possibly a scaled-down cake without any stacking required.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title5">Tiered Wedding Cakes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description6">Wedding cakes have come a long way from the days  ...  and white frosting. Today a talented cake designer using the new cake making tools and secrets along with ...  in mind in order to create a spectacular cake for your big day.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title6">The Perfect Wedding Cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description7">King cake, when referring to the New Orleans custom,  ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title7">Tips for locating an exceptional King cakes online instructional resource</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description8">...  say: it is just icing on the cake. You say that to mean that such ... , the essence of a particular thing. In wedding cakes, however, you cannot say the same thing ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title8">Not Just Icing on Wedding Cakes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description9">Have you just graduated? Do you have your birthday this month? Do you want to enhance the happiness of your happiness? If yes, then you must order a cake to accompany you in your celebrations.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title9">Mouth Watering Cakes Enhancing The Celebrations!</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description10">Do you want to give a truly memorable baby gift, one that isn't merely the same as what everyone else gives? It can be difficult to think of a great baby gift to give on a special occasion such as the birth,</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title10">Nappy Cakes</Content>
</ContentNode>
<ContentNode>
<Content Mapping="Description1">Cake pops are one of those snacks that more and more people are craving. They are incredible and inexpensive.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title1">How To Make Cake Pops</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description2">If you love cake decorating, imagine getting paid to do what  ... ! You can when you start your own cake decorating business or cupcake business. Jennifer James, author of the FabJob Guide to Become a Cake Decorator, says there are many benefits when ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title2">Should You Start A Cake Decorating Business Or Cupcake Business?</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description3">Hand mixers or food mixers are among the most important equipments that are required in a kitchen. No matter, what type of food you are preparing, you need to blend or mix a few ingredients to make your recipe perfect.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title3">Buy Hand Mixers to Make Your Job Easier In Kitchen</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description4">Wedding cake keeps varying according to their size, shape, occasion and flavor. Wedding cake comes with different flavors like chocolate, vanilla, raspberry, mango and many others to mention.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title4">Wedding Cake Pictures</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description5">...  celebratory moment of the wedding, is the cake cutting ceremony. It is a ritual, which has ...  its roots from the western culture. The cake cutting ceremony for the marriage is witnessed ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title5">Wedding Cake- The Sweetest Marriage Ceremony</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description6">There are infinite numbers of wedding cakes that are available. You can select the best one that suits your pockets, theme and personal preference.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title6">Types of Wedding Cakes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description7">Birthday cake ideas like size, flavors, designs and decorations.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title7">Ideas for Special Birthday Cakes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description8">Today we have cake decorators and beautiful cakes in the bakeries, the grocery stores, discount  ...  childhood and perhaps yours. Velvet Crumb Cake is a small square cake with a crumb topping that is ...  with coffee or tea. The Pineapple Pound Cake is perfect served with fresh fruit or ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title8">Old Fashion Cake Recipes for Velvet Crumb Cake and Pineapple Flavored Pound Cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description9">Couples prefer wedding anniversary cakes similar to the wedding cakes ordered for their wedding. This will help them to relive those exciting and intimate moments again.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title9">Wedding Anniversary Cakes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description10">Baking a cake can be a fun and also helps you  ...  opportunity to treat or gift a love one. Cake tins are the molds which can be used to prepare the cake according to the shape you desire by ...  the essential which is used for baking a cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title10">Baking Cake tins</Content>
</ContentNode>
<ContentNode>
<Content Mapping="Description1">...  a little different when it comes to ordering cakes for special occasions. As you will discover ...  do a search online for companies that make unique cakes Sydney that you are spoilt for choice ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title1">How To Choose The Right Company That Makes Cakes Sydney</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description2">You may ask, what are the best cake decorating kits? I can say there are a lot. There are cake decorating kits for students, and there are cake decorating kits for pastry ...  like myself. With such a large selection of cake decorating kits to choose from I can help ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title2">Best cake decorating kits</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description3">Bread machine are available in all shapes and sizes. Discover which one is the best.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title3">Take a Suggestion from Me and Make Sure You Get a Bread Machine</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description4">Gone are the days of the traditional wedding fruit cake layered in marzipan and coated in white icing. Today’s brides and grooms are mixing it up with a huge range of wedding cakes to choose from.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title4">Wedding Cake Advice</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description5">Every bride wants her wedding day to be perfect. Every detail is carefully considered and planned. The wedding cake is no exception</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title5">Enjoy A Custom Wedding Cake With Monogram Cake Toppers</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description6">Sunflower wedding cakes are the best option for the wedding ceremony. There are plenty of exotic designs which could be selected for the cake.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title6">Sunflower Wedding Cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description7">...  to keep in mind when buying wholesale cake boxes and paper carry bags for your ...  the wonders of the Internet, finding the cake boxes with the best prices has never ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title7">The Different Choices Of Cake Boxes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description8">...  of a wedding reception is the wedding cake. The cake is generally one of the main focal ... . So now you have found that ideal cake, how about you now consider an elegant ...  complete its look? Silver wedding cake stands not only look good but they also make a statement.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title8">Choosing the ideal silver wedding cake stands for your wedding</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description9">The wedding cake is one of the central elements of  ...  celebrated events of the wedding ceremony. Wedding cakes are expected to be tasty, decorative and ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title9">Wedding Cake Trends and Traditions</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description10">Above all, you need to understand that most private bakeries charge per "slice" instead of per "cake".</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title10">The Best Strategies To Get Cheaper Wedding Cake Prices</Content>
</ContentNode>
<ContentNode>
<Content Mapping="Description1">This article is on how to use chocolate as the part of the main ingredient in baking a chocolate flavor cake.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title1">Using Chocolate in Making Cakes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description2">...  be a fun and rewarding hobby. Everyone loves cake, and there's nothing more rewarding than presenting a loved one with a magnificently decorated cake that you made yourself. Like all new skills, learning how to decorate cakes will take time but the rewards are ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title2">Learn How To Decorate Cakes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description3">...  in particular are always very keen to make sure that their food looks as appealing ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title3">Commercial Advertising Photography - Making The Camera Lie In Order To Tell The Truth</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description4">The history of cake decorating is long. However, to cut to the chase, the cake is the ever present item when it comes to party.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title4">A Look at a Brief History History of Cake Decorating</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description5">Although there are quite a few ways to dress up a cake, one of the most fun and unique ways is with cake jewelry and cake toppers</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title5">Dress Up That Cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description6">...  want a plain crab cake, a crab cake dipped in a great dipping sauce, or a crab cake sandwich, the dish ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title6">Maryland Crab Cakes - As Good As It Gets</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description7">... . Though, there are many wedding themes, wedding cakes are always present. Today, there are various styles of wedding cakes. Their prices differ as well. In this ...  will discuss the different components of wedding cakes and why their prices vary.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title7">Guidelines in Choosing Cake For Your Wedding</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description8">Wedding cakes should be eye-catching and tasty, but  ...  between you and the ultimate wedding cake. Have your cake (and eat it too) with these ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title8">7 Ways to Save on Wedding Cakes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description9">...  the cake shop to select the best cake. You will get amazing cakes at the Online Cakes shops ...  anything from cakes to flowers, toys, books and any thing that you think will make someone ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title9">Amazing Cakes Online</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description10">Easter cake decorating ideas for you to create a stunning Easter cake this year. Easy cake decorating ideas, easter cake decorating photos and videos. Happy Easter!</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title10">Easter Cake Decorating Ideas That Are Too Cute To Eat</Content>
</ContentNode>
<ContentNode>
<Content Mapping="Description1">Perhaps you must want to make something special for your dear ones on some special days like birthday, anniversaries or when the guests come to your house uninformed. You may be at a loss to find out something new on every occasion</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title1">Bake Pops to Add New Dimension In Making Cakes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description2">...  no doubt that bride, groom and wedding cake are the three main elements in every ...  wedding cake. But do you know what the most significant piece of wedding cake is? Yes, a cake ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title2">Custom Wedding Cake Toppers- Match Your Wedding Perfectly</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description3">It would be wrong to say that cooking is experiencing a new found popularity these days because people have always had to eat and cook but there is a certain celebrity status to cooking these days.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title3">Cookers and Ovens Make Your Kitchen Come Alive</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description4">...  any kind of shower however, a wedding shower cake is an important part of the occasion ...  bride to be to a special wedding shower cake with these ideas.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title4">Great Ideas for your Wedding Shower Cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description5">... " ceremony. All eyes will be on the cake and how it looks. That said, even ...  is save money, that doesn't mean the cake should look like a piece of garbage. After ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title5">Saving Money On Your Wedding Cakes Designs</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description6">This article provides information on the benefits of ordering cakes online.This article provides information on the benefits of ordering cakes online.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title6">The Benefits of Cake Delivery</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description7">...  are considering wedding cakes as work of art. The old - fashioned wedding cakes are already the ...  cakes? The secret is that they have a wide array of wedding cake supplies at hand. Wedding cake designers must grasp the cake decorating kits that ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title7">How To Choose The Right Wedding Cake Supplies</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description8">...  hours to spend in our kitchens baking cakes. When I am pressed for time and need a nice dessert cake, I will reach for a box of chocolate cake mix. I don't bake just plain cakes, I like to add things to them to make them ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title8">A Fancy Twist On Chocolate Cake Mixes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description9">...  these versatile Christmas cake decorating ideas, you can use them to make your cake colorful and attractive ... , go ahead and enjoy these wonderful designer cakes with your loved ones. Merry Christmas and ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title9">New Year Delicious Christmas Cake Decorating Ideas Written - This Christmas Recipe with Delicious Christmas Cake Decorating Pattern</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description10">If you are a keen admirer of sweet food stuffs, then cakes will surely be on the top of your priority list. Cakes are considered to be the most delicious and delectable desserts.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title10">Explore Through Varied Options of Eggless Cake Recipe</Content>
</ContentNode>
<ContentNode>
<Content Mapping="Description1">All that you all use to express your feelings is using chocolates that are very good in taste as well as delicious.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title1">Soft Baking chocolate which is used commonly for making cakes and bakery items</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description2">Several bundt cake pan mixtures are available nowadays. This makes cake lovers bake at their own to save time and money. There are numerous bundt cake ...  trying out at the stores. Buying these cake mixes are very good deals. This would ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title2">Different Mixtures For Bundt Cake Pans</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description3">There has been a fashion of decorating the wedding cake with a cake top, which is known as cake topper and sometimes custom cake topper that is not new. The couples have been doing this for quite a long time and enjoying it.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title3">Secret behind the use of custom cake topper</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description4">Delicious chocolate wedding cakes are becoming more and more popular and make a great alternative to traditional fruit cakes.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title4">Unique and Delicious Chocolate Wedding Cakes For Your Big Day</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description5">Thinking about cabo san lucas destination wedding, looking for a wedding cake specialist to bake your cake is a sturdy job.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title5">Cabo San Lucas Wedding Cake Designer</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description6">The crab cakes can make good dishes for your lunch and your breakfast. Depending on the quantity to be consumed you can big crab cakes or small ones. Mustard sauce on top of it makes it taste better.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title6">Crab cakes, the most favorite dish of the coastal region of America</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description7">... ! If you're looking for 1st birthday cake designs, then I may just have a few ideas ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title7">1st Birthday Cake Designs</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description8">...  end, it is tradition that the cake is cut. A wedding cake is the signature of a wedding and no wedding ceremony can ever be complete without a cake. The sweet nature of cake just shows you how marriage ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title8">Choosing a Wedding Cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description9">By decorating the wedding cake yourself, you can save money, while also  ...  plans for the cake decoration. So, use your creativity and make your wedding cake unique and memorable</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title9">Latest Cake Decorating Secrets for Weddings - Current Wedding Cake Decorating Tips to Decorate Centerpiece of Your Wedding</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description10">See black and White Wedding cakes types, designs and decoration ideas in detail.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title10">Black and White Wedding Cakes</Content>
</ContentNode>
<ContentNode>
<Content Mapping="Description1">Cake decorating is a fun activity for all ages. In fact, a cake is a universally liked and preferred dessert item. Every house wife makes it a point to learn to bake a cake.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title1">How to Make Cake Decorating a Fun Activity</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description2">The wedding cake can be expensive and eat up a lot of your wedding budget - and it may not even get eaten at the end of the day. In this article, we explore some great ways to get a great-looking wedding cake that won't break the bank.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title2">How to Save Money on Your UK Wedding Cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description3">...  suggest pushing yourself to sending a gift of cake or a bucket of flowers from the vast ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title3">Celebrate Your Precious Occasion with Hyderabad Cakes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description4">The term "cake" is becoming very popular among the city dwellers as different types of occasions and ceremonies need various types of cakes.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title4">Buy Cake Online- anytime any moment</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description5">This article will introduce you to wedding cakes and how they play an important role in weddings.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title5">Importance of Wedding Cakes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description6">... 're on a birthday cake hunt and you want the most perfect cake ever to please your ...  age maybe, grown men enjoy cool birthday cakes as much as younger boys do! They ...  toned down, unlike girls, but give a man a cake shaped like a cigar or a golf course (yes ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title6">5 Cool Birthday Cakes for Men Ideas that Will Make All Men Drool</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description7">The benefits of making cake recipes from scratch and how to make it easy to create a cake from scratch.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title7">Mastering Easy Cake Recipes From Scratch</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description8">For a delicious and gorgeous layer cake, make this Savannah Praline-Spice Cake. It looks and sounds complicated ...  is easy. It starts with a boxed carrot cake mix and also uses canned frosting. But ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title8">Savannah Praline-spice Cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description9">If your cake decorating designs do not come out to  ...  beginners' small mistakes. After all, anything you make with love will be enjoyed and appreciated ...  home.Unique Instructions to Decorate Your Own Cakes - Different Cake Decorating Designs to be Appreciated by ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title9">Unique Instructions to Decorate Your Own Cakes - Different Cake Decorating Designs to be Appreciated by Everyone at Home</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description10">A cake lover and expert greatly present his or her work of art through the exquisitely decorated cakes and pastries.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title10">Cake Carrier: Every Cake Lover's Mistress Of Help</Content>
</ContentNode>
<ContentNode>
<Content Mapping="Description1">...  to the kitchen? There was almost always a cake waiting to be enjoyed at my grandma's house and just thinking about those cakes is enough to make my mouth water. If you ...  fashion cake recipes for some real treats! Homemade Amish Cinnamon Coffee Cake and Chocolate Chip Date Cake ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title1">How to Make Cakes Like Grandma Did - Amish Coffee Cake and Chocolate Chip Date Cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description2">...  that can't be forgotten about is the cake. Every celebration needs a focal point and the perfect one is by having a custom made cake. This not only adds individuality and personality ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title2">Cakes Stratford</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description3">you can wish anyone through gift in every occasion like birthday. Cakes are the best option regarding this. Now Hyderabad cake shop make the way to sending gifts to Hyderabad very much easiest.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title3">How Can We Send Birthday Cake to Our Own People</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description4">Summer wedding cakes are available in different designs and flavors. Summer wedding cakes are available in the light yellow or white color for the cake.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title4">Summer Wedding Cakes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description5">Want your wedding cakes designs to be beautiful, yet have no idea how to make that happen? Then the answer is simple, use these methods &amp; techniques to spark your imagination and get those creative juices flowing!</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title5">Wedding Cakes Designs - Great Ways to Spark Your Creativity</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description6">...  tired of boring parties with store bought cakes and stale desserts? This happens all too ...  anniversary party could be with specialty Miami cakes made specifically for the event. Specialty made ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title6">Tips for Dressing up a Party with Specialty Miami Cakes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description7">...  occasions and events. Entertaining your guests with cakes in different occasions is one of the ...  functions in the unique ways, with 3 tier cake stand you can fulfils your purpose. Now ...  to get the big size cake but you can use 3 tier cake stand to do so.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title7">3 Tier Cake Stand</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description8">This combination of peanut butter and chocolate combines into one perfect cake. You can impress your family and friends without a lot of trouble on your part.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title8">Peanut Butter Creme Fudge Torte Cake for a Sweet Treat</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description9">Birthday cake decorating ideas can be as creative as you make them. If you've liked these ideas, use your imagination to make some more innovative ones.Birthday cakes are special and what makes them even ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title9">Great Birthday Cake Decorating Ideas to Love - Proper Cake Baking Decorating Techniques You will Surely Love</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description10">As per the tradition, a day before the wedding, the bride to be is given an opportunity to celebrate a night with her family and family. The fun filled night is known as wedding shower.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title10">Cakes for Wedding Showers</Content>
</ContentNode>
<ContentNode>
<Content Mapping="Description1">...  her house were always special and the cakes she would set out were something to ...  grandmothers kitchens that are different. Chocolate Potato Cake used mashed potatoes in the batter and the Dark Spice Cake is made without eggs or milk.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title1">How to Make Cakes Like Grandma Made: Chocolate Potato Cake and Dark Spice Cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description2">Cake decorating techniques make use of special skills in handling sugar frosting besides other techniques to attain brilliantly finished cakes which are visually breathtaking not to mention be edible.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title2">Cake Decorating, Why Study the Techniques Employed by Experts?</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description3">Your wedding should be one of the most memorable days in your life. Before you even start planning the wedding there are many details you need to see too. The first thing you and your finance need to discuss is how much you are willing to  ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title3">How Much to Spend on Your Wedding Cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description4">If you've never given a specialty cake as a present, you're really missing out  ...  opening up a box and seeing a delectable specialty cake inside. If you're seeking an incredible ...  five reasons why you should choose a specialty cake.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title4">5 Top reasons to Give Gourmet Specialty Cakes as Presents</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description5">Choosing your wedding cake can be a costly and stressful process if not done correctly. This article will provide a brief guide to help you make your decision less stressful.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title5">Choosing Your designer wedding cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description6">...  a significant transformation to the idea of sending cakes to Bangalore or flowers to Mumbai. The ...  has made, even sending delicate gifts like cakes, easy to send.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title6">Ways for Sending Cakes to Bangalore in the Modern Age!</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description7">...  of cake stands three tier cake stand is one of the most terrific and popular cake stand ...  parties. In a very decent manner three tier cake stands not only used to manage the ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title7">Three Tier Cake Stand</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description8">Do you want to know how I make choosing birthday cake pans easy? If you are new ... , then perhaps choosing the right shape of cake pan is something you've been struggling ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title8">The Easy Way to Choose Birthday Cake Pans</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description9">These 50th birthday cake decorating ideas will help you to make a tempting treat for the person ... , along with an attractive birthday cake, can definitely help you make the birthday truly memorable for ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title9">Attractive Birthday Cake Decoration Ideas for Person Turning 50 - Interesting 50th Birthday Cake Decoration Concepts</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description10">...  adorn their wedding ceremony cake having a cake topper of some type. Wedding ceremony cake toppers are available ... . From exquisite monograms to fun and humorous cake toppers, you'll obtain some thing special to crown your wedding ceremony cake in model and place a personal touch in ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title10">Your Wedding Cake Topper</Content>
</ContentNode>
<ContentNode>
<Content Mapping="Description1">Most of us find happiness in cooking delicious treats for our loved ones. Many people find it a perfect stress buster in the busy life. If you too love to cook good food, trying on new recipes can be exciting and fun.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title1">Discover the Quick to Make Cake Recipes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description2">... , cousins, grandparents and the list goes on. Cake is the chief source of celebration as ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title2">Sending Cakes Online for Multiple Birthday Parties</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description3">...  so many occasions when we require custom cakes. Occasions such as birthday celebration, a wedding, an ...  together to celebrate a happy moment, presence of cake makes the occasion more delightful and elegance.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title3">Custom Cakes Toronto: Designed to A Graceful Occasion</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description4">Valentine's Day Cakes are also very popular nowadays as they are ideal option to pamper your beloved and shower affection.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title4">Find Varieties of 5 star Cake Online</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description5">Cakes and cup cakes are always a fun treat for anyone. Try some of these easy cake recipes using pre-packaged cake mixes and little extra ingredients. Get creative by decorating your cakes with different cake flavours and frosting.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title5">Cup Cakes &amp; Cakes of All Types</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description6">If you want to make a cake that is easy to put together but  ...  recipe for a Coconut and Orange Marble Layer Cake. This cake starts with a boxed mix and the ...  from the grocery store shelf. Yet this cake is very tasty, very pretty, and may ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title6">This Coconut and Orange Marble Layer Cake Recipe Starts With A Boxed Mix But Becomes a Classic</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description7">...  married couple cut the cake together it symbolizes unity. The Wedding Cake is very popular in modern culture. When selecting a wedding cake there are some ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title7">Wedding Planning - How to Select a Wedding Cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description8">Try one of these old fashion chocolate cake recipes for a delicious treat for family and friends. Whether you choose Bittersweet Chocolate, Dutch Mocha Chocolate or Cherry Devil's Food, it is sure to please the chocoholics in your group.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title8">Grandma's Old Fashion Chocolate Cake Recipes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description9">...  for making triple chocolate cake. Triple chocolate cake calories is around 728 for a medium-sized cake, so this cake ...  treat yourself occasionally and bake this wonderful cake for a special dinner.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title9">How to Bake Triple Chocolate Cake for a Special Valentine Dinner - How to Make Homemade Perfect Triple Chocolate Cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description10">People who travel a lot for professional reasons often miss special occasions to celebrate with family and friends.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title10">Cut Short Distances by Sending Cakes Online</Content>
</ContentNode>
<ContentNode>
<Content Mapping="Description1">I will give you a link to where you can view a video of how to make a Cake! I will be telling you how to make a Chocolate cake ;), Yummy one at that!</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title1">How to make cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description2">...  the right place. Here are some cake baking and cake decorating ideas and information. Baking and decorating cakes is one of the fascinating things to  ...  or with friends. Here is information on cake recipes with tips on baking and decorating ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title2">Master The Technique of Baking Cake in The Field of Baking and Decorating Cake - Information on Cake Recipes with Tips on Baking and Decorating</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description3">... : cookies, mince pies, Christmas pudding, Christmas cake. The Christmas cake should be prepared well ahead of ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title3">Grandma's Old-Fashioned Chocolate Cake With Chocolate Icing</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description4">The tradition of wedding cakes started very long time ago, dated as  ...  ancient Greece, in fact people say wedding cake is as old as wedding it self ...  was not to cut the cake, instead the groom breaks the cake over the wife's head ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title4">Wedding Cake Prices-Simple Facts About Wedding cakes and their prices</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description5">...  to include in your party is a delicious cake.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title5">Cake – A Favorite Party Food</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description6">If you are not a fan of edgy wedding cakes and would prefer a more conventional wedding cake, then worry not, as traditional wedding cakes come in a variety of popular forms and shapes.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title6">Traditional Wedding Cake Ideas</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description7">The texture and taste for considering the right kind of frosting for your cake decorating.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title7">The Science Of Cake Frosting</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description8">Chocolate wedding cake is highly demanded in wedding season. Generally it is liked by all people of any age say from small children to adults. Mostly, chocolate wedding cake is liked by children very much.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title8">Chocolate Wedding Cake Designs</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description9">...  ice cream cake is sinfully tempting. But, if you are calorie conscious then make a note that chocolate ice cream cake calories can be somewhere near 400 calories. So, make ...  to learn a recipe for chocolate ice cream cake? Then scroll down to know a simple method ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title9">Do You Want to Learn a Recipe for Chocolate Ice Cream Cake? - Simple Method of Preparing Chocolate Ice Cream Cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description10">The news of arrival of a young one in the family is a moment of joy not only for the parents but also for the grandparents and close friends and relatives.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title10">Baby Shower Cakes Avaliable</Content>
</ContentNode>
<ContentNode>
<Content Mapping="Description1">...  as using special cake boxes and making personalized T-shirts that kids will love to make your party ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title1">Make Your Birthday Party Special by Making Cake Boxes for Your Children</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description2">...  is imperfect and forgettable without that special cake and it also retains a special meaning in ...  become pretty much mandatory these days. The cakes are generally baked at very high temperature ...  think about celebrating a birthday with no birthday cake. Unique coloring combinations…flavors and toppings are ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title2">No special day complete without having a celebration cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description3">You can make your life partner happy and always laughing  ...  wedding by gifting him/her a wedding cake with a cake topper denoting your love. This is the ...  probably to do something with your wedding cake.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title3">Secret of wedding cake topper</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description4">New Year wedding cakes come in the most unique varieties and with elaborate designs. You can go in for a huge white wedding cake which is quite popular nowadays.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title4">New Year Wedding Cakes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description5">The “How to” on Cake – When … … You Don’t Know Thing About Baking!</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title5">How to - Cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description6">...  almost every occasion. We celebrate with cake, we share cake with family and friends over coffee ...  a fantastic meal with a piece of cake. We even enjoy giving cakes as gifts from time to ...  our lives. Add these recipes to your cake recipe files.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title6">Let 'Em Eat Cake - Mini Gingerbread Cakes and Applesauce-Raisin Tube Cake Recipes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description7">Information and ideas about the different types of cupcake boxes, and tips the choosing the right cake box for your baked goodies.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title7">Cake Decorating - As Easy As 1,2,3</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description8">Take these simple steps to prepare your cake for cake decorating and you will have better results.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title8">Improve Your Cake Decorating Results With Proper Cake Preparation</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description9">Delicious and Excellent Chocolate Cake Frosting Recipes - Sumptuous Chocolate Cake Frosting Recipes Online..Check out some sumptuous chocolate cake frosting recipes.Chocolate Cake Frosting</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title9">Delicious and Excellent Chocolate Cake Frosting Recipes - Sumptuous Chocolate Cake Frosting Recipes Online</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description10">Wedding cakes are available in different shapes, sizes, flavors. Lots of ideas come in our minds when we think about cakes.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title10">Wedding Ideas - Cakes</Content>
</ContentNode>
<ContentNode>
<Content Mapping="Description1">Cake decorating frosting recipes can sure come in handy. In cake decorating, frosting or icing is the most important part.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title1">How to Make Cake Decorating Frosting Recipes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description2">Find Cakes Online in Bangalore and types of Cakes. Different Home Delivery cakes are Birthday Cakes Bangalore, Wedding Cakes Bangalore, Party Cakes Bangalore, Photo Cakes Bangalore, Chocolate Cakes Bangalore and Cheesecakes.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title2">Order Cakes in Bangalore</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description3">...  at home moms who are struggling to make ends meet.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title3">How I started my successful home based cake decorating business</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description4">The history of the grandiose multi-tiered wedding cake is as interesting, if not more so, than the cake itself. Also, a number of traditions were tied to the wedding cake reflective of cultural beliefs of times long past.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title4">History and Tradition of Wedding Cakes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description5">The article discusses the different types of cakes flavors and designs. It emphasizes on benefits of sending cakes through online sites and also suggest online portal for sending cakes to Pakistan</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title5">Nothing better than a Delicious Cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description6">...  to make sure its perfect for the day. When it comes to a significant birthday the cake ...  be forgotten. It's no use buying a supermarket cake, that's bland in taste and decoration. You want a spectacular and unique cake that's suited to the individual.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title6">Custom Cakes Warwick</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description7">...  wedding planning process could possibly be wedding cake. Not just the couple but guests anticipate ...  too. Just like a bride's wedding dress, the cake should also be as beautiful. You desired ...  that dream is having those layers of cake at the reception.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title7">Tips to Help You Save on Your Wedding Cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description8">... , you laughed at the videos of wedding cakes melting, falling down, trampled upon by nature ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title8">Three Wedding Cakes Disasters You Want to Avoid</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description9">You can customize your wedding cake or cake design to make it a mesmerizing one for the ceremony. You can go in for some unusual designs to embellish your wedding cake.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title9">Customize your Wedding Cakes</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description10">Your marriage reception is not really a reception without a wedding cake. It has become common to stack countless cake layers to make one gigantic cake. Currently, marriage cakes are wore interested in taste and demeanour,</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title10">Changing Trends in Wedding Cakes</Content>
</ContentNode>
<ContentNode>
<Content Mapping="Description1">To master the cake making arts entirely, one actually has to go  ...  cakes should be like. It is of course impossible for us, amateur cake baking fans to make perfectly good looking and delicious cake at the very ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title1">How to Make a Cake from Scratch – Some Cake Making Thoughts</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description2">To bring a perfect shape to the cake, the cake tins are very useful. Beginners can use the can tins very well to make cakes.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title2">Types And Uses Of Cake Tins</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description3">The best way to make an ordinary cupcake extraordinary is by getting stylish laser cut wrappers and then putting them in a beautiful favour box, so get some today to go extraordinary.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title3">Make Your Cupcakes Extraordinary</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description4">You can celebrate this festive season with the most beautiful Christmas cake. This task could be more exciting, if you decorate the cake on your own.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title4">Easy Ways to Decorate Your Christmas cake</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description5">If you are looking for easy but impressive cake recipes, this article has several to offer!</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title5">Easy Cake Recipes for Baking Newbies</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description6">Miami is known for its parties and celebrations, and its baked goods and pastries are no exception.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title6">Miami: Cakes and Cupcakes Have Come of Age</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description7">...  you kidding?" he questioned, "How can I send cake to India from New York?" he wondered ...  aware of the ways he can send cake to India.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title7">The Quickest way to Send Cakes to India</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description8">Cakes as we all know are the best kind of dessert there is. Apart from being a popular dessert, cakes are also a delicacy for some traditional events such as weddings or birthdays.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title8">What Cakes Can Give</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description9">... . Only a few near and dear ones can make the occasion a memorable one too. Birthdays can ... , you can make it even more special by Sending Cakes Online. It will make your dear one feel special and more loved. Birthday cakes can ...</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title9">Cakes-The Perfect Birthday Gift</Content>
<Content Mapping="Description10">...  of a post-wedding party is the wedding cake.</Content>
<Content Mapping="Title10">Wedding cakes for celebration</Content>
</ContentNode>
</Page_Content>
</Project>
